I am so bored.
Hey, dog, when you take a break
from re-applying your lipstick,
- how about taking me to the park?
- My lipstick? What?
Oh, right, right.
Right, because of my penis.
Yeah, that's fantastic.
Lois, Brian won't take me to the park.
Then he talked about his ding-dong.
Lois. Lois!
Damn it, woman! Pay attention to me!
Stewie, that's not nice.
Don't grab Mommy's pants like that.
You could really hurt her.
Yes. Yes, I could, couldn't I?
I could hurt Mommy.
Shame on us, Rupert.
How dare we succumb to boredom
while that wretched woman
continues to breathe?
She must be destroyed.
With Lois out of the way,
I could finally focus on my life's ambition
of taking pictures of Madison County.
Let's go back and take a bath.
Yeah. How about you go back
and take a bath?
Griffin, have you filed
those shipping reports yet?
Angela, Angela, come here. Check this out.
Look at what this chick is doing
to this polar bear.
Wait, wait...
Wait, wait, wait. It's coming up.
There you are, Opie.
Congratulations.
You made Employee of the Month again.
How come I'm never
Employee of the Month?
Man, this is the worst job I've had
since I was the conductor
for the Sand People choir.
And a one and a two.
No, no, no, no! The altos were early.
This is the worst glee club I've ever...
Come on. Where are you going?
- The benefit's tomorrow!
- Relax.
The Sand People frighten easily
but they'll be back.
And in greater numbers.
Well, that'll give us a richer harmony.
Oh, yeah. No, it's gonna sound fantastic.
Help! Somebody! I'm blacking out.
Brian, help me.
That jerk, Opie,
got Employee of the Month again.
All because my boss hates me.
Maybe you need to brown-nose her
a little bit, Peter.
Really? I thought you said she was ugly.
Oh, you mean kiss up to her.
That's a great idea, Joe.
And if that doesn't do it, you could
always just work hard and be polite.
That's how I won friends
when I worked for E!
Seabiscuit! Seabiscuit!
Would you mind talking to E!?
I'm not Seabiscuit. I'm Penelope Cruz.
And you're just lovely.
Would you like a carrot?
Good girl.
Brown-nose, huh?
All right. I'll do something special for her.
Surprise!
Griffin, what the hell
are you doing at my house?
Well, I asked around the office
and everybody said you liked animals,
so I organized a surprise cockfight.
Oh, boy. Oh, boy. Oh, God.
Well, looks like they killed each other.
That's probably what all that racket was
about an hour ago.
Well, I will see you Monday.
Oh, crap.
Well, looks like the good Lord
just sent me a conversation starter.
Come here, Jesse. Come get the ball.
How unfortunate.
Miss Hobson, Stewie's really been
acting out a lot at home.
And I was just wondering,
how's he been behaving at school?
Mrs. Griffin, let me show you
some pictures he drew in class.
- Notice anything unusual?
- I sure do.
- His father's not in any of them.
- Exactly.
Well, Peter's been very preoccupied
with work lately.
I guess Stewie's been missing his father.
Thank you for letting me know.
Damn! She moved.
Well, I suppose it's not the first time
someone's made a miscalculation.
What happens to us in the future, Doc?
It's your kids, Marty. Something's
gotta be done about your kids.
- What do you mean?
- Your daughter marries a black man.
- That's actually not a big deal for me.
- Yeah, me neither.
Well, it... Well, it... You... Really?
Yeah. I mean, what's wrong with that?
No, no, nothing, nothing.
It's nothing, I guess. I think it's great.
Congratulations.
I don't think I'm comfortable
around you anymore.
Did you know peanut butter
was invented by a black man?
Too late, Doc.
Hi, Herbert. What brings you here?
It seems your son's baseball
broke one of my windows the other day.
Oh, my God. I am so sorry.
Chris, this is gonna come out
of your allowance.
Perhaps we could work something out.
I could use a strapping young man
to do some chores around my house.
That seems fair to me.
Chris, you have damaged
this man's property.
And until you pay off the debt,
you'll do whatever job he wants you to do.
And at the end of the day,
if you're exhausted
and your face is dripping wet, well,
that just means you did a good job.
That sounds fine.
I don't want to spend my weekend
doing chores.
You know, Chris,
a little hard work can do wonders.
Just look at how they built the pyramids.
They say all peoples
must go through some hard times.
Well, we Jews are getting ours
out of the way early.
From here on out,
it's gonna be nothing but smooth sailing.
I have an announcement to make.
Don't you do it.
Don't you lose a single pound.
I don't care what
those Hollywood image-makers say.
Big women are sexy.
I wanted to tell you
that Opie will not be receiving
Employee of the Month,
because he's being promoted.
Oh, yes!
That means I'm Employee of the Month.
No, you're not, Griffin.
I'm giving it to Soundwave.
So, I can just put my stuff anywhere?
My wife, Denise.
We met in a Christian chat room.
- Peter, we need to talk about your son.
- The fat one or the funny-looking one?
Dad called you fat.
Wait.
Stewie's really been acting out lately.
And, I think it's 'cause
he's not spending enough time with you.
It's time that you take an interest
in your son.
Starting today, I want you to spend
more time with Stewie.
Okay.
You can make a box fort.
See? Here's a box.
You can pretend it's a fort.
Actually, that sounds like fun. I want this.
I'm king in here.
Peter, maybe Stewie
would like to play fort, too.
No! If you need me, I'll be in space.
Great idea bringing Stewie
to Fenway Park, Peter.
Yeah. There's no better place
for a father and son
to really get to know each other
than a ballgame.
Where is Stewie?
Is that a baby in there?
Oh, my God! He's gonna miss the game.
Hey, you guys.
You remember those hot homeless twins
who live under the overpass?
Well, last night I...
Wait, wait, Quagmire.
Let me cover Stewie's ears.
And this is the hand
that caused all the trouble.
Got your nose, little guy.
Peter, did you take Stewie to a strip club?
He smells like sweat and fear.
Let me tell you, Tuesday afternoon
is not exactly their A squad.
I actually saw bullet wounds.
You can't just take him places
you want to go. He's a baby.
Look, Lois, I think I know how
to spend time with my own kid, all right?
The bond between a father and son
is sacred.
I'm sorry, Jesus. But my house, my rules.
Up yours, Joseph. You're not my real dad.
- Hello?
- Hey, Dad, it's me.
Listen, things here
aren't working out anymore.
And I was just... I was wondering,
can I come live with you and Janet
for a while?
Wow, kiddo. You know, I'd love that,
but I don't know if now is the best time.
Maybe next year, okay?
I'll see you Friday night.
Tell your mother I sent the check.
- So, where were we?
- Right about here.
- Come on, baby, it's my birthday.
- No.
All I'm saying is that
you just need to find an activity
that you and Stewie can share.
Peter, can you reach that box of rice?
Oh, sorry, Lois.
That rice got you, bitch.
Hey, Stewie's laughing.
Hey, you think that's funny?
Hey, you like that?
Hey, Lois, you want some beans
with that rice?
I misjudged you, fat man.
Damn it. Peter, what's wrong with you?
Wait, Lois, Lois, don't move.
Stewie's loving this.
See if she's got any cash on her.
Okay, Stewie, get the camera ready.
Peter, stop it!
What the hell are you doing?
What do you think I'm doing?
I'm bonding with Stewie.
There is nothing more precious
than a baby's laughter.
- Jeez, I hope she can get out.
- I'm sure she'll be fine.
Well, hello there, young man.
I was starting to think
you weren't coming.
Sorry I'm late, Mr. Herbert.
Well, I guess I'll get started.
You know, if you get sweaty
and want to take your shirt off,
that'd be just fine.
Or tie it in a knot, your choice.
We now go live to Ollie Williams
in the Channel Five traffic copter.
- What's the scene, Ollie?
- Everybody looks like ants!
Probably because you're up so high.
Coming up next,
an exclusive interview with Andrew Shue.
Hey, hey, Dad, Dad, pull my finger.
Wait... Sounded like a peep toad.
But it's not summer.
Hey, drippy. You're back.
What's for dinner?
Peter, when I said bond with Stewie,
this is not what I had in mind.
- I am furious with you!
- You can't talk to him like that.
Take that!
- Stewie, you're going to your room.
- I think not, Dad's got my back.
Stewie, she looks mad.
You better go to your room.
What's the matter with you, fat man?
Stop her. Help me, you fool.
You traitor.
I trusted you but you're a wuss!
Don't feel bad, Peter.
Hey, I know what'll cheer you up.
- No, I don't think I'm in the mood.
- Are you sure?
Sorry, Brian. It's just not doing it today.
Hey, Stewie.
You got a minute for your daddy?
Get out of here, you spineless oaf!
Oh, and by the way,
I faked all those bowel movements.
Brian, I feel awful.
Stewie and I were getting along so good
and now he hates me.
- How do I get him to like me again?
- Well, that depends.
Do you really want my advice or are
you just asking random questions again?
What's a hypotenuse?
Stewie, I know you're a little mad at me
right now.
But, when you see where I'm taking you,
you're gonna change your mind.
Yeah, right. I'm gonna change my mind.
We just sat on a plane for three hours
to come to Florida, God's waiting room,
for who knows what...
Disney World! Disney World!
Disney World!
I want to go to Disney World!
Disney World! Disney World!
I'm still mad at you.
Hey, check it out, Stewie.
Halle Berry's Wild Ride.
Wow! It looks like
Michael Jackson's coming right at me.
I say, we've been puttering around
this fat farm for hours. I've had enough.
Hey, Stewie, they got... Stewie?
Oh, my God, he's gone.
Has anyone seen my son? Hello?
Hey, it's the crows from Dumbo.
Hey, you guys seen my son?
Well, I done seen about everything but
I sure enough ain't seen your boy, no how!
That's good old-fashioned family racism.
Well, well, a lost child.
Looks like we've got a new recruit.
- Now sing.
- I shall do no such thing.
You must sing.
If you don't, they'll make you do
a Christmas movie with Tim Allen.
Is Chris still doing chores
for that disgusting old man?
Meg, that's not nice.
Old people have a lot to offer society.
Just look at Kim Catrall.
Come and get it, big boy.
Oh, damn.
There we go.
Thanks for buying me dinner, Mr. Herbert.
I wanted to thank you properly
for all your hard work.
- Souvenir photograph?
- Hell, yes.
Are you dead?
I say, fat man. Get me out of here.
Stewie, there you are. Thank God.
Why are you dressed like Rerun?
You're free, children. Run back
to your individual countries of origin.
Hey!
Those multi-cultural slave children
belong to the Disney Corporation.
Get them, Achmed.
Hey, look over there.
There's a woman learning.
Quick, in here.
Looks like we're in the clear.
- Michael Eisner.
- Cover your heart.
Kali Ma!
You betrayed the shareholders.
You think he's dead?
No, no. He'll be back on his feet in no time,
probably follow
in Jonathan Dolgen's footsteps,
wind up with a pod deal
over at Touchstone.
You all right, Stewie?
You know what, fat man?
I'm not sure how to say this
without sounding cheesy,
but, well, you really came through
for me today. So I...
What the hell.
I love you, too, buddy.
Come on, Stewie. Let's go home.
Florida. Just think,
somewhere in this state right now,
Jeb Bush is eating a live puppy.
Well, Jesse, I guess we got to find
some other way to spend our evenings.
And now back
to ESPN's exclusive coverage
of the Little League World Series.
Oh, jackpot!
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru